Milne School; Records ua659
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Principal's Correspondence Files, 1952-1973; 4; 3.33 cubic ft.
  - Profile, 1975-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 26)
  - Promotions and Continuing Appointment Criteria, Undated (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 27)
  - Promotions and Continuing Appointment Policies, 1971-1973 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 28)
  - Promotions and Continuing Appointment Policies, 1974-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 29)
  - Promotions, Tenure, 1974-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 30)
  - Pupil Personnel Committee, 1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 31)
  - Records Inventory, 1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 32)
  - Regents Scholarship Exam Security Procedures, 1975-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 33)
  - Regents - Scores, Exams, Report (See confidential series), Undated (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 34)
  - Registration, 1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 35)
  - Registration, 1976-1977 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 36)
  - Reorganization Plan, 1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 37)
  - Requirements, Courses for Milne Students, 1975-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 38)
  - Research Material, 1972-1973 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 39)
  - Retrenched Faculty Assistantships, 1977 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 40)
  - Retrenchment, 1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 41)
  - Retrenchment Efforts, 1975-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 42)
  - Retrenchment Positions, 1977 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 43)
  - Room Assignments, 1974-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 44)
  - Rules and Regulations, 1974 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 45)
  - Rules and Responsibilities, 1976-1977 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 46)
  - S.A.T. Exam, Reports (See confidential series), Undated (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 47)
  - Schedule Attendance, 1972-1973 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 48)
  - Schedules and Rooms, 1972 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 49)
  - School Accounts, 1974-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 50)
  - School Accounts, 1975-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 51)
  - School Accounts, 1976-1977 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 52)
  - School Districts, 1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 53)
  - School of Education Colloquia/SUNYA, 1974-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 54)
  - School of Education Load Cards, 1974-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 55)
  - School 1-Troy/Milne, Joint Meeting, 1973 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 56)
  - Selective Salary Increase, 1973-1974 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 57)
  - Selective Salary Increase Policy, 1973-1974 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 58)
  - Selective Salary Increase Policy, 1975-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 59)
  - Senior Class, 1973 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 60)
  - Senior Class Diplomas, etc., ca. 1970 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 61)
  - Space Committee-Downtown Campus, 1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 62)
  - Special Subjects and Course Descriptions, 1975-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 63)
  - Spielman File-Issues, 1974-1977 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 64)
  - Staffing - Personnel Office Records, 1972 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 65)
  - Stage School, ca. 1970 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 66)
  - Stage School, 1974 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 67)
  - Structured Classroom - Rules and Schedule, 1973-1974 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 68)
  - Student Achievements, 1974-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 69)
  - Student Association Accounts, 1972-1973 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 70)
  - Student Association Accounts, 1972-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 71)
  - Student Data-Course Recommendations, 1973-1974 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 72)
  - Student Fees, 1974-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 73)
  - Student Government Constitution, 1973-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 74)
  - Student Handbook Material Not Used, 1973-1975 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 75)
  - Student Handbook Proposed, 1975-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 76)
  - Student Honors, 1975-1976 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 77)
  - Student Roster, 1970s (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 78)
  - Student Roster, 1973-1974 (Box 18 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 79)
  - Student Roster, 1974-1975 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 1)
  - Student Roster, 1975-1976 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 2)
  - Student Summer Activities, 1972 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 3)
  - Student Teacher Assignments, 1974-1975 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 4)
  - Student Teacher Handbook, 1972-1973 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 5)
  - Student Teachers, 1972-1973 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 6)
  - Student Teachers, 1975-1976 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 7)
  - Student Teacher's Material, 1974-1976 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 8)
  - Student Teacher's Office, 1972-1975 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 9)
  - Student Teaching Experience Evaluations, 1971 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 10)
  - Supervisor Load, 1972-1973 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 11)
  - Teacher Education, 1970-1973 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 12)
  - Teacher Evaluation - Socrates, 1962 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 13)
  - Teacher Training Apprenticeship Program, 1972 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 14)
  - Teachers - New York State Legal Definition, Undated (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 15)
  - Teachers Schedule, 1976-1977 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 16)
  - Textbook Requests, 1973 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 17)
  - Theodore Fossieck, Corresponence, 1964-1968 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 18)
  - Theodore Fossieck, Corresponence, 1969-1973 (Box 20 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 1)
  - Three Year Plan, 1973 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 2)
  - Troy Project, 1972-1973 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 3)
  - University Center School, 1974-1975 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 4)
  - Utilities, Inventory of, 1974 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 5)
  - Video Taping Equipment, 1970 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 6)
  - Workshop, BOCES, 1973-1974 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 7)
  - Workshop, 1972 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 8)
  - Yucatan Inter-American Studies Program, First, 1972 (Box 19 (4-Principal's Correspondence Files), Folder 9)
- Closing of Milne, 1952-1977; 5; 1.2 cubic ft.
  Materials are related to the Closing of the Milne School and include annual reports, legislation related to the school, and committee notes.
  - AD HOC Committee on Campus Schools, Part 1 - Report, 1971 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 1)
  - AD HOC Committee on Campus Schools, Part 2 - Report, 1971 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 2)
  - Committee on the Use of the Laboratory School, 1967-1969 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 3)
  - Committee on the Use of the Laboratory School, 1969-1972 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 4)
  - Community Relations Including Phase Out, 1967-1975 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 5)
  - Faculty Association, 1970-1972 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 6)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1969-1970 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 7)
  - Fiser Report Evaluating Milne, 1967-1970 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 8)
  - Fretwell Report Data-Departmental Justifications of Milne School, 1971 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 9)
  - Future of Milne Committee, 1952-1967 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 10)
  - Gardner, Dean - School of Education Correspondence and Memos, 1966-1969 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 11)
  - Lab School Committee, 1967 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 12)
  - Lab School Phase Out-[RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 13)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Patrons must consult an archivist before viewing this material.
  - Lab Schools, N.Y.S., 1968-1969 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 14)
  - Lab Schools, N.Y.S., 1969-1970 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 15)
  - Lab Schools, N.Y.S., 1971-1972 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 16)
  - Lab Schools, N.Y.S.-AD HOC Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 17)
  - Lab Schools, N.Y.S.-Legislation, 1970-1971 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 18)
  - Lab Schools, N.Y.S.-Milne Specific, 1971-1972 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 19)
  - Lab Schools, N.Y.S.-Principal's Meetings, 1970 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 20)
  - Lab Schools, N.Y.S.-Principal's Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 21)
  - Master Plan, 1970s (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 22)
  - Master Plan, 1971-1972 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 23)
  - Memoranda, 1975 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 24)
  - National Council For Accreditation of Teacher Education (NCATE), Undated (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 25)
  - Report, Part 1, 1969-1970 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 26)
  - Report, Part 2, 1969-1970 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 27)
  - Research Committee, 1971-1972 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 28)
  - Three Year Plan, 1972-1974 (Box 20 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 29)
  - Legislative Resolution, 1977 (Box 21 (5-Closing of Milne), Folder 1)
- Confidential Testing and Ranking Files, 1907-1977; 6; 2.0 cubic ft.
  Restricted due to the presence of student grades. These records cannot be made available due to the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (FERPA). Please consult an archivist for more details.
  Series is made up of scores from various tests, and class rankings from 1948-1977.
  - Admissions Testing, 1968 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 1)
  - Admissions Testing, 1969 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 2)
  - Admissions Testing, 1969-1970 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 3)
  - Admissions Testing, 1970 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 4)
  - Admissions Testing, 1971 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 5)
  - Admissions Testing, 1972 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 6)
  - Admissions (Tests and Grades), 1972-1973 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 7)
  - Attendance Records, 1959-1960 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 8)
  - Class, 1930-1945 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 9)
  - Class, 1948 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 10)
  - Class, 1949 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 11)
  - Class, 1950 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 12)
  - Class, 1951 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 13)
  - Class, 1952 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 14)
  - Class, 1953 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 15)
  - Class, 1954 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 16)
  - Class, 1955 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 17)
  - Class, 1956 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 18)
  - Class, 1957 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 19)
  - Class, 1958 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 20)
  - Class, 1959 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 21)
  - Class, 1960 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 22)
  - Class, 1961 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 23)
  - Class, 1962 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 24)
  - Class, 1963 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 25)
  - Class, 1964 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 26)
  - Class, 1965 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 27)
  - Class, 1966 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 28)
  - Class, 1967 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 29)
  - Class, 1968 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 30)
  - Class, 1969 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 31)
  - Class, 1970 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 32)
  - Class, 1971 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 33)
  - Class, 1972 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 34)
  - Class, 1973 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 35)
  - Class, 1974 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 36)
  - Class, 1975 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 37)
  - Class, 1976 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 38)
  - Class, 1977 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 39)
  - Final Averages/Rank - Post High School Plans, Undated (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 40)
  - National Merit Qualifying Test, 1960-1968 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 41)
  - Regents Answer Booklet, 1975 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 42)
  - Regents Diploma Applications, 1946-1967 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 43)
  - Regents Exams, 1960 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 44)
  - Regents Exams, 1960-1963 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 45)
  - Regents Exams, 1963-1965 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 46)
  - Regents Exams, 1965-1967 (Box 22 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 47)
  - Regents Exams, 1965-1970 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 1)
  - Regents Exams, 1967-1968 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 2)
  - Regents Exams Series, 1966 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 3)
  - Regents Exams Series, 1967 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 4)
  - Regents Exams Summanry, 1907-1960 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 5)
  - Regents High School Exams, Undated (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 6)
  - Biology, 1970 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 7)
  - Biology, 1971 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 8)
  - Chemistry, 1970 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 9)
  - English, 1970 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 10)
  - English, 1975 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 11)
  - English II, 1976 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 12)
  - French III, 1971 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 13)
  - Latin II, 1971 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 14)
  - Math 9, 1970 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 15)
  - Math 9, 1971 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 16)
  - Math 10, 1970 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 17)
  - Math 10, 1971 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 18)
  - Math 10, 1975 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 19)
  - Math 10, 1976 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 20)
  - Math 11, 1970 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 21)
  - Social Studies, 1970 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 22)
  - Social Studies II, 1975 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 23)
  - Social Studies II, 1976 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 24)
  - Regents Papers Written, 1973 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 25)
  - Regents Principal's Report, 1907-1910 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 26)
  - Regents Principal's Report, 1911-1913 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 27)
  - Regents Principal's Report, 1914-1917 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 28)
  - Regents Principal's Report, 1918-1922 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 29)
  - Regents Principal's Report, 1923-1927 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 30)
  - Regents Principal's Report, 1928-1932 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 31)
  - Regents Principal's Report, 1933-1937 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 32)
  - Regents Principal's Report, 1938-1941 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 33)
  - Regents Principal's Report, 1942-1945 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 34)
  - Regents Principal's Report, 1946-1953 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 35)
  - Regents Principal's Report, 1954-1964 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 36)
  - Regents Scholarship Exams, 1962-1965 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 37)
  - Regents Scholarship Exams, 1960-1971 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 38)
  - Student Failures, 1974 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 39)
  - Test Results, 1960-1965 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 40)
  - Test Results, 1966-1967 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 41)
  - Test Scores, 1973-1974 (Box 23 (6-Confidential Testing and Ranking Files), Folder 42)
- Scrapbooks, 1909-1953; 7; 2.0 cubic ft.
  Materials are arranged chronologically.
  Series is made up of several scrapbooks documenting events at the Milne Schoo, as well as the lives of students and faculty. Includes materials like newspaper clipppings, pamphlets, and photographs.
  - Scrapbook, 1909-1929 (Box 24 (7-Scrapbooks), Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1930-1939 (Box 24 (7-Scrapbooks), Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1939-1940 (Box 24 (7-Scrapbooks), Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1941 (Box 24 (7-Scrapbooks), Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1942-1943 (Box 24 (7-Scrapbooks), Folder 5)
  - Scrapbook, 1943-1945 (Box 24 (7-Scrapbooks), Folder 6)
  - Scrapbook, 1945-1946 (Box 25 (7-Scrapbooks), Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook, 1946-1947 (Box 25 (7-Scrapbooks), Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook, 1949-1950 (Box 25 (7-Scrapbooks), Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook, 1949-1950 (Box 25 (7-Scrapbooks), Folder 4)
  - Scrapbook, 1935-1953 (Box 25 (7-Scrapbooks), Folder 5)
- Student Association and Student Council Records, 1921-1976; 8; 2 cubic ft.
  This series is made up of administration materials for the Student Associaiton and Student Council, including materials such as financial reports, constitution, meeting minutes, and correspondence.
  - Balance Sheet, 1960-1968 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 1)
  - Balance Sheet, 1969-1970 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 2)
  - Balance Sheet, 1970-1971 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 3)
  - Balance Sheet, 1971-1972 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 4)
  - Balance Sheet, 1975-1976 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 5)
  - The Bear Facts, 1967-1968 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 6)
  - Budget, 1947-1949 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 7)
  - Budget, 1949-1950 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 8)
  - Budget, 1952 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 9)
  - Budget, 1965 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 10)
  - Budget, 1969 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 11)
  - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 12)
  - Cash Book, 1955-1960 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 13)
  - Cash Book, 1942-1948 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 14)
  - Constitution, 1950s (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 15)
  - Constitution, 1965-1971 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 16)
  - Correspondence Regarding Student Pins, 1936-1937 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 17)
  - Diploma-Samples, 1939; 1972 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 18)
  - Directory, 1935-1936 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 19)
  - Excuse Slips, 1937 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 20)
  - Financial Journal, 1958-1969; 1961-1967 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 21)
  - Financial Reports, 1933-1934 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 22)
  - Financial Reports, 1935-1939 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 23)
  - Financial Reports, 1939-1940 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 24)
  - Financial Reports, 1939-1941 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 25)
  - Financial Reports, 1940-1941 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 26)
  - Financial Reports, 1941-1942 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 27)
  - Financial Reports, 1942-1943 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 28)
  - Financial Reports, 1943-1944 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 29)
  - Financial Reports, 1944-1945 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 30)
  - Financial Reports, 1945-1946 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 31)
  - Financial Reports, 1946-1947; 1947-1948 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 32)
  - Financial Reports, 1965-1974 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 33)
  - Financial Reports, 1969-1976 (Box 26 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 34)
  - Financial Register, 1961-1965 (Box 27 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 1)
  - Financial Reports, 1975-1977 (Box 27 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 2)
  - Junior High-Life, 1962 (Box 27 (8-Student Association and Student Council Records), Folder 3)